A comedy that hits you right where it counts.
Barry Munday is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Chris D'Arienzo.
Barry Munday, a libido-driven wage slave who spends all his time either ogling, fantasizing about or trying to pick up
women, wakes up in hospital after a freak attack only to find that his testicles have been removed.
Barry Munday, played by Patrick Wilson.
Mr. Farley, played by Malcolm McDowell.
Ginger Farley, played by Judy Greer.
Jennifer Farley, played by Chloë Sevigny.
Lida Griggs, played by Missi Pyle.
Heavy Metal Greg, played by Colin Hanks.
Barry Munday (alternatively known as Family Jewels) is a 2010 American comedy film directed by Chris
D'Arienzo; it is based on the novel Life is a Strange Place by Frank Turner Hollon.
It is D'Arienzo's directorial debut.
The film stars Patrick Wilson as the title character, as well as Judy Greer, Chloë Sevigny, Jean Smart,
Shea Whigham, Missi Pyle, Christopher McDonald, Billy Dee Williams and Malcolm McDowell.
The story revolves around a womanizer who wakes up to find that his testicles have disappeared
and he is facing a paternity lawsuit by a woman he can't remember having sex with.
The film premiered at the South by Southwest Film Festival on March 13, 2010, got picked
up by Magnolia Pictures and was given a limited release on October 1.
Barry Munday garnered negative reviews from critics who praised Wilson's performance but
criticized D'Arienzo's quirky filmmaking leading the vulgar material.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
pregnancy, letter, castration, paternity.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.